Good evening! I'm Hanako Akimoto. I'm Hanako Akimoto.
I love games,
I'm not very good at it,
I have an older brother, so I grew up playing games all the time.
This New Year's, I spent all day playing Pokemon,
I was forever looking for different-colored Pokemon,
I was playing Pokemon and searching for different colors forever,
That's how much I like games,
I like games, right? Plus, I like ice cream, right?
I have just the thing for you!
And it's this one!
De-da-da-da-da! Pinoge!
We used to play this game called "Pinot Love" on Ice TV,
It's called "Inga Simulation Game",
The game was about falling in love with Mr. Pinot and trying to get a happy ending,
I got a pad end, at that time.
But it was super fun! It was fun.
It was so much fun,
They've been releasing various kinds of Pinoy games!
They started last October,
One of them is called Pinot's Rhythm!
I like rhythm games too!
I play a rhythm game of "Prince of Tennis" called "TENILABY" anytime I want.
I'm always playing a rhythm game of "Prince of Tennis" called "Tenilaby".
I'd like to play yesterday's rhythm game again.
I'll open the game now.
Yesterday's voice was so shocking.
Since then, we've received a lot of comments from fans that they've done the game.
Some of them had happy endings.
Wow!
Some of you are good at love?
Yes! Yes, for sure!
Well, it was difficult!
It looks like this.
I love the package!
I want it! Heart! I want it! Heart! I want it! Heart!
Oh, that's too bad.
I'd like to play the game by clicking the QR code with my cell phone.
A new type of ice cream rhythm game!
Tap functions in rhythm
Make a beautiful shape and do the pokey
Game
Yes!
Ah! You can start Pinot rhythm!
Then, start!
This is the place where a certain Dr. Pinot is building his factory.
In order to make the site of making Pinot delicious Pinot more fun
Dr. Rhythm Pinot production line was created by Dr. Rhythm Pinot
Pick the Pinot that flows into the Rhythmic Pinot Production Line in a rhythmic way!
If you get it right, a nifty melody will echo through the factory, and the Pinot will be delicious!
Now, let's make lots of delicious Pinot with your skill!
Songs to choose from
Easy is Sweet Pinot
Pinot Love on Normal
Let's go for Pinot Love!
I'll do it! Pinoy love!
Is the sound on? I didn't play any sound.
OK!
On the way, the palms are going to start playing.
Can you hear it?
All right, let's go for perfect.
Happy music.
Rangers!
Here we go!
Unfashionable music.
I see what you're getting at.
So they're playing everything but Pinot on the side.
This is not pinot.
Sometimes they play Pinot with a heart.
Calories?
Oh, uh, this is Dobon.
Ihnen.
Oh, there it is.
It's fun.
But the background music is too pop.
Stylish.
And it's amazing that you can play for such a long time, isn't it?
It's free. It's not free, it's the price of a pinot.
Oh, wait!
I can't connect.
It's okay.
I almost had a full combo.
What?
Huh.
But?
Yes, I got an S.
I got an S. Now go to the top.
Oh, wait, I think I have to get a full combo to do the next one.
I heard that a full combo on EASY OR NORMAL will release this one!
Okay, let's do it again.
At what point do you eat the ice cream?
Mushrooms... I had a timing to eat it, but...
Now.
Mmm~~
Let's try Easy, change the song.
If we can get a full combo on this one, let's try the next one
Okay, okay
Oh, great!
You're so sweet.
Eh?
Pinopinopita.
Thank you for watching.
It's kind of calming, isn't it?
Oh, it shows up next to
It's called pinot pinot, or a fake pinot.
Mock pinot?
It's not pinot.
There's something in the middle.
This is Parm.
It's not Pinot.
Parm.
This Pinot
Heart Pinot
Palm
Pinot, Pinot!
It's Pinot!
It popped!
It's fun.
Do you guys do that?
Rhythm games?
Love Live is a rhythm game, right?
That's true.
I think so, and I think everyone does it.
I think so... I think so... I think so... I think so... I think so...
Adm.
Pinot!
Pino! Pinot!
Ah! Star Pinot!
Palm! Oh, it's Parm.
Pinot!
Pinot! Pinot!
Palm!
Dumb Pinot! Dumb Pinot!
Pinot!
What? Did I get it?
Huh?
Combo.
Ah! A full combo!
Yay!
Look at the combo.
Yes!
If you do that...If you do that...
Ah! I can now do the last hard one!
Try this last one.
Keep cheering!
Okay.
Oh! That was fast!
Happy's line is early!
Happy's line, early!
Early!
That's great, great, great.
Oh, oh, I missed it!
I mean, it's been about this long since I started this, and that's the number of taps I just did.
Easy.
Okay, let's go for "S".
All right. Oh, what's that?
I don't see any powermisses.
Oh, this is fun.
Oh, no, no, no. I couldn't tap.
Here we go.
Wow.
Whew!
I'll do my best.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
From here on out, no more mistakes.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's a little tight.
The line is tighter than a drummer.
Wow.
I'm all right, I'm all right.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
You have to hit it right here.
Miss...
Aah! Miss first!
Aah!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This can't be happening.
I need more...
Come on!
Oh, she's drinking water, Riza!
Oh, no!
Wow.
But it's fun.
Heh, no.
I was flat.
I kinda want to do this every time I eat.
And I like the music. It's very stylish.
Oh, you're ranked 8173rd. How many of you are doing this?
8173rd, huh? That's frustrating.
Well, I'm going to keep working hard to get to the top of this list.
So this time, I'd like to introduce Pinoy Rhythm by Pinoy Geisha.
There are about 4 more kinds? So I guess there are 6 kinds in total.
And there are 4 more kinds of Pinoys and Puyopuyo...
I'm also interested in Puyopuyo.
There's also a racing game, so please give it a try!
Please give us a try! Please leave a comment, click the "Good" button, and subscribe to our channel!
See you later, ice cream!
♪